A Finding Aid to the C. J. (Clarence Joseph) Bulliet Papers, circa 1888-1959, in the Archives of American Art AAA.bullclar
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1919-1952; Series 4; 20 Linear feet Boxes 5-24
  - Marlow, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Maroto, Gabriel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Marquet, Pierre Albert, 1938-1941 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Marsh, Fred Dana, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - Marsh, Reginald, 1931-1938 (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Marshall, Ben, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - Marshall, Harriet, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - Martial, Lucien, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Martin, Benito Quinquela, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 102)
  - Martin, Gail W., 1936 (Box 16, Folder 103)
  - Martin, Homer Dodge, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - Martin, Keith, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - Martin-Ferrieres, Jac, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 106)
  - Martinet, Marjorie D., 1929 (Box 16, Folder 107)
  - Martorell, Bernardo, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Marval, Jacqueline, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Maryan, Hazel Sainaiko, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - Marzolo, Leo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 111)
  - Masakichi, Hananuma, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 112)
  - Masereel, Frans, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 113)
  - Masolle, Helmer, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 114)
  - Mason, Alice, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 115)
  - Masquerier, J. J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  - Massare, Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - Masson, Andre, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - Masson, Antoine, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 119)
  - Master Andre, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 120)
  - Master E. S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - Master of Alkinaar, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 122)
  - Master of St. Sang, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 123)
  - Master of St. Veronica, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - Master of the Half-Length Figure, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 125)
  - Master of the Life of Mary, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - Master of the Nuremberg Passion, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - Master of the Playing Cards, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - Master of the Von Groote Adoration, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Matheur, Harriet E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - Matisse, Henri, 1927-1948 (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - Matsys, Q., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - Matta, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - Mattern, Karl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 134)
  - Matthews, A. Lou, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 135)
  - Mattson, Henry, 1931-1935 (Box 16, Folder 136)
  - Matulka, Jan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 137)
  - Maufra, Maxine, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - Mauncy, Jacques, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 139)
  - Maurer, Alfred, 1924-1934 (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - Maurin, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - Mauve, Anton, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 142)
  - Mayer, Henrik M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 143)
  - Mayer, Leo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 144)
  - Mayhew, Neil Broolsen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 145)
  - Mazzanovich, Lawrence, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 146)
  - McAllister, Mary, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 147)
  - McBarron, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 148)
  - McBey, James, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 149)
  - McBurney, James E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 150)
  - McBurney, Thomas E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 151)
  - McCarthy, Helen K., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 152)
  - Machach-Kala, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 153)
  - McCormack, Nancy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 154)
  - McCormick, A. D., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 155)
  - McCormick, Amy Irwin, 1932-1940 (Box 16, Folder 156)
  - McCortan, Edward, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 157)
  - McCosh, David, 1932-1934 (Box 16, Folder 158)
  - McCracken, James, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 159)
  - McCrady, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 160)
  - McEvoy, Ambrose, 1924-1939 (Box 16, Folder 161)
  - McFee, Henry Lee, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 162)
  - McIntire, Samuel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 163)
  - McKenzie, R. Tait, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 164)
  - McKillop, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 165)
  - McKinnie, Mirioue, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 166)
  - McKnight, Dodge, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 167)
  - McKnight, Robert J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 168)
  - McLane, M. Jean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 169)
  - McMein, Neysa, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 170)
  - McPhersen, Marie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 16, Folder 171)
  - Mechau, Frank, Jr., 1935 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Meckenem, Israhel van, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Medgyes, Ladislas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Medina, H., 1930 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Meeker, Chris Marie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mege, Violette, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Meierhans, Joseph L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Meissouier, J.L.E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Melcarth, Edward, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Melchers, Gari, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Meltsner, Paul, 1931-1940 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Memling, Hans, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Memmi, Lippo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Menard, Emile Rene, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Mendelsohn, Erich, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Mengarini, Fausta, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Mengarini, Vittoria, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Menghi, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Menkes, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Menzies, William Cameron, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Merchi, Gaetan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Merida, Carlos, 1935-1941 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Mero, Lee, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Meryon, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Mesnier, J. L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Mestrovic, Ivan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Metcalf, Willard L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Metzinger, Jean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Metzl, Ervine, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Metzu, Gabriel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Meunier, Constantin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Meux, G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Meyer, Herbert, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Meyerowitz, William, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Mezquita, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Michalov, Ann, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Michaudel, Arthur, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Michel, Georges, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Michelangelo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Micheli, Armand G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Michelson, A. A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Michetti, Francesco Paolo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Mielziner, Jo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Miervelt, Michiel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Mikkelsen, Karl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Millar, Clyde, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Miller, Barse, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Miller, Edgar, 1934-1936 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Miller, Hugh, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Miller, Iris A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Miller, Kenneth Hayes, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Miller, Richard E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Milles, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Milleson, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Millet, Clarence, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Millet, Jean François, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Millhouser, Harry L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Millier, Arthur, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Millon, Elizabeth B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Mills, Florence, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Minkenberg, H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Minne, Georges, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Mintz, Harry, 1938-1940 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Miro, Joan, 1925-1940 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Misick, Henry D., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Mitchell, Glen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Mittelstadt, M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Mizon, Frederic, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Mochi, Ugo, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Modigliani, Amedee, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Moeller, Gustave, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Moessel, Julius, 1934-1946 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Moffett, Ross, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Moholy-Nagy, Laszlo, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Molas, H. de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Mold, Pier Francesco, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Moms, Maximilian, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Mondrian, Piet, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Mondzain, Simon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Monet, Claude, 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 80-81)
  - Monnickendom, Martin, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Montanari, Giuseppe, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Montenegro, Roberto, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Monticelli, Adolph Joseph Thomas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Monvaerni, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Moody, Helen Wills, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Moore, Benson B., 1930 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Moore, Bruce, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Moore, Henry, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Moorepark, Carton, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Mora, F. Luis, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Morales, Luis de, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Morales, Theodore, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Moran, Thomas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Morandi, Giorgio, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - More, Herman, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Moreau, Louis Gabriel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - Moreelse, Paulus, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Moret, Henri, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - Morgan, Charles L., 1933 (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - Morgan, Edith, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - Morgan, Herbert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - Morin, Jean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Morisot, Berthe, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Morland, George, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Morley, Hubert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Moro, Antonio, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Moroni, Gianbattista, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - Morris, Cedric, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Morris, LeRoy D. M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Morrison, David, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - Morrow, Elmer, Jr., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Morrow, Julie Mathilde, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - Morse, Samuel F. B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - Mortimer, J. H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Mosby, William H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 117)
  - Mose, Carl C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 118)
  - Mose, Eric, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 119)
  - Maselio, Simon, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 120)
  - Mosman, Warren T., 1931 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Mostaert, Jan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - Motley, Archibald J., Jr., 1933 (Box 17, Folder 123)
  - Mouillot, Marcel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 124)
  - Mousseau, Roland, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 125)
  - Mowbray, H. Siddons, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 126)
  - Moy, Seong, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 127)
  - Mrozewski, Stefan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 128)
  - Mucha, Alphonse, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 129)
  - Mueller-Oerlinghausen, B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 130)
  - Mulholland, W. S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 131)
  - Muller, Daniel C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - Muller, Otto, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - Mulligna, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 134)
  - Mullin, Charles Edward, 1930-1933 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Munch, Edvard, 1944-1954 (Box 17, Folder 136)
  - Munnings, A. J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  - Munns, E. E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - Munzer, Adolph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Murilli, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - Murillo, Bartolome Esteban, 1928-1930 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - Murmion, Simon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 142)
  - Murphy, Christopher, Jr., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 143)
  - Murphy, H. Dudley, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - Murphy, J. Francis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 145)
  - Musick, W. E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 146)
  - Myers, Frank H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 147)
  - Myers, Irwin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - Myers, Jerome, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 149)
  - Mystkowski, C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 150)
  - Nack, Kenneth G., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - Nadelman, Eli, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - Nagler, Fred, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - Nagy, Sigismond de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 154)
  - Nakian, Reuben, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 155)
  - Nanatueil, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 156)
  - Narozny, Helen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - Nash, Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 158)
  - Nash, Joseph R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 159)
  - Nason, Thomas W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 160)
  - Nathier, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - Nattier, Jean Marc, circa 1888-1959 (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - Nauman, Arno, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - Neagle, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Neblett, Walter G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Neebe, Louis Alexander and Minnie Harms Neeble, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Neebe, Minnie Harms, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Negulesco, Jean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Neilson, Raymond P. R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Neroccio, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Nesbitt, Philip, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Ness, Kenneth, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Neuhys, Albert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Nevinson, C.R.W., 1929 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Newberry, John K., 1935-1942 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Newberry, Max, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Newton, Francis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Newton, H. H., 1928 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Newton, Lilas T., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Newton, Milledge, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Nicholls, Bertram, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Nichols, Dale, 1937-1939 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Nichols, Hobart, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Nielsen, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Nielsen, Kay, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Nielson, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Nielson, John A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Nielzinger, Leo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Nilsson, Carl J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Nisbet, C. B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Nisbet, Robert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Noble, John, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Noecker, Harold, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Noguchi, Isamu, 1932-1935 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Nolde, Emil, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Nolf, John Thomas, 1935-1939 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Nordan, Maxa, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Nordhausen, Henry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Nordstroem, Karl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Nordstrom, B.J.O, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Norman, Viola, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Northcote, James, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Norton, John W., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Norwood, Ruth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Noyes, Florence, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Noyes, George L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Nura, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Nutley, Harold P., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Nutting, M. C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Nuyttens, Pierre, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Nyholm, Arvid, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Oakley, Violet, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - O'Bear, Mary Virginia, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - O'Brien, Dermid, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Oberteuffer, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Oberteuffer, H. Amiard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Oberteuffer, Karl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Obrovsky, Jakub, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Ochtervelt, Jacobus, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Ochtman, Dorothy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - O'Connor, Andrew, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Ogden, Roe, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - O'Hara, Eliot, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1926-1943 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - O'Keeffe, Ida Ten Eyck, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Oldfield, Otis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Olinsky, Ivan, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Olmsted Brothers, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Olofsson, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Olsen, Carl, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Olstowski, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - O'Malley, Power, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Onyx, Max von, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Opie, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Oppi, Ubaldo, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Oppo, Cipriano Efisio, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Opsomer, Isidore, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Opstad, A. Anderson, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Opstad, Adolf A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Oppenheimer, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Orb, Helen Ruth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Orley, Bernard van, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Orlik, Emil, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Orloff, Chana, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Orloff, Gregory, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Orr, Alfred Everitt, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Orozco, Jose Clemente, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Orpen, William, 1925-1931 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Osborn, Frank, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Ossian, Elgstrom, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Osthaus, Edmund C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Ostrenga, Raymond, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Ostrowsky, Abbo, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Ostrowsky, Sam, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - O'Sullivan, Sean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Ott, Jane Llewellyn, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Ott, Peter Paul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - Oud, J.J.P., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - Ouren, Karl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Owen, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Paalen, Wolfgang, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Pach, Walter, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Pacheco, Maximo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Paddock, Ethel Louise, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Page, Grover, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Page, Marie Danforth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Paine, May, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Palainedesy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Palenske, Reinhold, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Palmblad, Signe, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Palmer, Honore, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Palmer, Pauline, 1936-1950 (Box 18, Folder 109)
  - Palmer, Samuel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Pannaggi, Ivo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 111)
  - Parcell, Malcolm, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - Parker, George Waller, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 113)
  - Parrish, Maxfield, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 114)
  - Parshall, DeWitt, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 115)
  - Parshall, Douglass, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 116)
  - Parsons, Edith B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 117)
  - Parsons, Sheldon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 118)
  - Parton, Henry W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 119)
  - Partridge, Roi, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 120)
  - Pascin, Jules, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 121)
  - Pascoe, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 122)
  - Patlageau, Numa, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 123)
  - Patterson, Charles R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 124)
  - Patterson, Howard Ashman, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 125)
  - Patterson, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 126)
  - Pattison, Abbott L., 1940-1948 (Box 18, Folder 127)
  - Patton, Katherine, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 128)
  - Paul, J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 129)
  - Pauling, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 130)
  - Pauley, F., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 131)
  - Paulsen, Henry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 132)
  - Paulus, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 133)
  - Paulus, Pierre, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 134)
  - Pauser, Sergius, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 135)
  - Pavlosky, Vladimir, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 136)
  - Pavon, Jose, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 137)
  - Payne, Edgar A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 138)
  - Payne, Mrs. Paul T., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 139)
  - Peale, Raphaelle, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 140)
  - Peale, Rembrandt, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 141)
  - Pearson, Edwin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 142)
  - Pearson, Ralph M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 143)
  - Pechstein, H. M., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 144)
  - Pechstein, Max, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  - Peiffer-Watenphul, Max, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 146)
  - Peirce, Waldo, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 147)
  - Pekary, Istvan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 148)
  - Pelikan, Alfred G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 149)
  - Pellegrini, Ernest, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 150)
  - Pena, A. X., 1938 (Box 18, Folder 151)
  - Pencz, Georg, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 152)
  - Pennell, Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 153)
  - Penzyna, C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 154)
  - Perdriat, Helene, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 155)
  - Perfilieff, Vladimir, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 156)
  - Perkins, Harley, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 157)
  - Perlin, Bernard, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 158)
  - Permeke, Constant, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 159)
  - Perreal, Jean, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 160)
  - Perrine, Van Deering, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 161)
  - Pescheret, Leon R., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 162)
  - Pesellino, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 163)
  - Petersen, Christian, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 164)
  - Petroff-Vodkine, Kuzma, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 165)
  - Peyraud, Angela Estelle and Bettie Jane Torrey, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 166)
  - Peyraud, Elizabeth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 167)
  - Peyraud, Frank C., 1935 (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - Peyton, Bertha Wenzler, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 169)
  - Pfeiffer, Heinrich, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 170)
  - Pfister, Jean Jacques, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 171)
  - Philbride, Allen Ersteine, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 172)
  - Philipp, Robert, 1936-1951 (Box 18, Folder 173)
  - Philips, Bert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 174)
  - Phillips, Holmead, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 175)
  - Phillips, John E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 176)
  - Phillips, Marjorie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 177)
  - Phillips, Thomas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 178)
  - Phillips, Walter J., 1928 (Box 18, Folder 179)
  - Philpot, Glyn, circa 1888-1959 (Box 18, Folder 180)
  - Picabia, Francis, 1929-1936 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Picasso, Pablo, 1928-1950 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
  - Piccarilli, Attilio, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Picken, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Pieper, Josef, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Pikelna, S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Pillat, J. Brates, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Pimenov, Iuri, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Pink, Harry, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Pinto, Angelo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 19, Folder 11)